Scenes from an Empty Church is a drama film directed by Onur Tukel.
In a locked-down NYC, two priests open their church doors to those
seeking salvation during the most isolating of times.
From the commonplace to the truly metaphysical, their visitors reflect
the full spectrum of personal crises of spirituality.
Throughout their encounters with the city's sweetest, wildest and weirdest, the two
priests learn the importance of connection, empathy and open-mindedness.
Sometimes a little faith is all you need to make it through the bad times.
Father Andrew, played by Kevin Corrigan.
Paul, played by Max Casella.
Father James, played by Thomas Jay Ryan.
Nurse Sara, played by Natalie Carter.
Elisabeth, played by Marjorie Johnson.
Anna, played by Eva Dorrepaal.
Many films have featured mid- and post-credits scenes.
Such scenes often include comedic gags, plot
revelations, outtakes, or hints about sequels.
The tone is emotional.